Today is a big day for us, that is, for ICICI Lombard.
Today, we organised a
safety awareness programme by
flagging off the rally and distributed films to at least
500 adults and 500 children
in the historic ground in the middle of the garden.
I would like to thank the people of Bihar and the people of Patna who
stood in large numbers since 8:00 in the morning
and enjoyed the rally. The
crowd was as big as ours, and we are doing
this kind of Awaaz programme and helmet
distribution for the first time in Bihar.
We liked it very much and we will make continuous
efforts in this way in small districts and
other districts of Bihar as well. We
currently have a programme to do this in 10 districts, so we are going to do
road safety awareness programme in 10 more districts,
Right to Safety and
ICICI Lombard, whose tagline is
Nibhaye Vaade Hum Vade Nibhana, believes in this.